http://kfai.org/about/privacy

Login
COVID-19 Testing Resources
Now Broadcasting
Voice Cried SoftlyTHE EVERLY BROTHERS - I\'m Here to Get My Baby Out of Jail
KFAI’s Covid-19 Volunteer Plan
KFAI, Fresh Air Inc., shares your concerns about privacy and is extremely committed to protecting the security of your personal information. This Privacy Statement explains the different types of information which we may collect from you and how that information may be used. We will not sell, share or rent the information you provide to us in any way that has not been specified in our Privacy Statement. If you have questions regarding this Privacy Statement or KFAI’s information practices, please contact us at webteam@kfai.org.
In several locations within this Site, KFAI requests personal information (including, but not limited to, name, mailing address, phone number and email address) in exchange for further information related to our various programs and the opportunities we may be able to offer you to become further involved with our organization.
Upon registering personal information with us, KFAI stores your information in various databases so that we may continue to provide you with information related to your interests. If you no longer wish to receive such information or to change your information, please contact us at webteam@kfai.org. Upon receipt of your request, KFAI, within a reasonable time period, will make specified edits to your information and / or remove your information all together from receiving future communications.
KFAI asks for personal information from anyone who chooses to make a financial donation to the station. When making an online gift, we request name, mailing address, phone number, email address and credit card information. This enables us to record and provide written acknowledgment of such contributions, as required by law.
KFAI does not rent, sell, swap, exchange or trade the names, email and mailing addresses, phone numbers, or any other submitted donor or listener information with other organizations or businesses, including to any political parties or organizations. All membership and payment information is collected using secured and encrypted Secure Socket Layers (SSL).
You may link to third-party web sites, such as those of our community partners and underwriters, through our web site. Once you have linked from kfai.org to a third-party web site, KFAI can no longer protect information you may share on the third-party web site, and the policies of the third-party web site will apply to your personal information.
Electronic communications from KFAI will provide the opportunity for you to unsubscribe from the KFAI email list. You also have the opportunity to opt-out of being a subscriber through our web site. Alternatively, you may email the Interim Program Director. Please include “Unsubscribe” in the subject header.
KFAI uses external financial corporations to process many of our charitable donations. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing us with these processing services.
Tweets
DONATE
Back to Top
Home
Get To Know KFAI
Contact Us
Donate/Support Us
On Demand
© 2020 KFAI – Minneapolis + St. Paul &dash All Rights Reserved.
1808 Riverside Avenue, Minneapolis, MN 55454 P: 612-341-3144
